

# Marcin Jakubiak in/marcin-jakubiak

I am a UX / UI designer. I develop myself in this field in January 2021. I have been carrying out freelance jobs since August 2021. I deal with UX after working hours and I continuously learn, design and prepare my professional portfolio. I have extensive experience working in an international team where the leading language is English.

### Education



### Wrocław University of Science

Field of study - Mechanical Engineering Faculty - Engineering of Aviation



**Become UX Designer** 



Become a User Experience Designer 11h learning path



**English level C** 

10.2016 - 02.2020



## **Experience**



### 🕒 LG Energy Solution

Innovation Specialist | Business Management Group | 06/2021 - present

My current job where I design and improve production processes. Projects are defined in accordance with a specific KPI and implementation is based on the research. I use 6 sigma, lean and PRINCE2 methodology.

(Define, Measure, Analyze, Improve, Control)

I also conduct Industrial Engineering trainings and direct the "Continuous Improvement Process" team.

#### Freelance Designer

UX/UI Designer 08/2021 - present

My portfolio website can be viewed at this link:

https://uxuimarcinjakubiak.netlify.app/

My freelance job mostly included a UI design,

from single components to full websites.

Currently, I work on a car rent website for Avion.

The status of my projects and my other works can be viewed at this link:

https://www.artstation.com/marcinjakubiak



#### Xeos (Lufthansa Technik & GE Aviation) 😪 🚳





Aircraft Engine Mechanic Trainee 03/2020 - 04/2021

I followed a 15-month training program to become an authorized GE-nx engine mechanic for the Boeing 747-8. I gained theoretical and practical skills related to servicing turbine engines, but also received training in aviation law, human factor, work organization and teamwork. Unfortunately, the training was not completed due to the suspension of the Xeos company, caused mostly the crisis on the aviation market.

## Hobby



design



singing



gaming





guitar

cars

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).